Hi, I'm Sonia and I'm here at South Woodford Blueprint Fitness.
A couple of years ago, I had a pretty bad medical, realised that I was spending all my time working
and on the kids and no time on myself, so I decided to make fitness a priority for me.
I am in ill-disciplined and I need motivation and so therefore I was looking for a PT,
but a one-on-one PT session where someone's kind of screaming in your face and you have to
chat a lot wasn't for me, so a small group PT is perfect. You get the individual support,
but you get to train with people, which for me is really motivating.
Which is fantastic here. They've all got their own way of training,
but they're all really supportive. They will come, they'll correct my form,
they will push me if I am taking it easy on any given day or if they think I've gone too far,
they'll pull it back or adapt it. I actually had major surgery in March of this year and
all of them helped me kind of get back into the gym and
adapted the exercises so that I could get back in my feet.